<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<!--/Defs/ThingDefs_Misc/Weapons/OG_AMA_Weapons_Tau_Melee.xml-->
                       <!-- honor blade (T) -->
<OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.label>клинок чести (T)</OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.label>
                             <!-- A Honour Blade is a weapon carried by Tau Ethereals and Ethereal Guards for a number of uses. It's mainly used as a symbols of their office, ceremonial weapons, and in self-defence. While each weapon is custom-made, they all feature a broad blade fitted to a long, lightweight metallic staff. Ethereals use the blades primarily to settle disputes, engaging in lengthy, highly stylised duels that are more coordinated co-meditation than combat. The combatants dance and weave as if in a trance, their weapons flashing past one another scant millimeters and microseconds from causing terrible damage. Yet somehow, the dance is always bloodless, as if the Ethereals are in total union with one another. In truth, the combatants are engaged in a deeply spiritual duel, conducted at a level which none outside of their caste can discern. Some Ethereals carry their Honour Blades on the field of battle, not expecting to have to use them, but prepared to make a last stand against their foes nonetheless. -->
<OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.description>Клинок Чести - это оружие, которое носят Эфирные Тау и Эфирные стражи для различных целей. В основном он используется в качестве символа их должности, церемониального оружия и в целях самообороны. Хотя каждое оружие изготовлено на заказ, все они оснащены широким лезвием, прикрепленным к длинному, легкому металлическому древку. Эфириалы используют клинки в основном для разрешения споров, участвуя в длительных, сильно стилизованных дуэлях, которые больше похожи на скоординированную совместную медитацию, чем на бой. Бойцы танцуют и сплетаются, словно в трансе, их оружие проносится мимо друг друга в считанных миллиметрах и микросекундах от того, чтобы нанести ужасный урон. И все же каким-то образом танец всегда бескровен, как будто эфирные существа находятся в полном единении друг с другом. По правде говоря, сражающиеся участвуют в глубоко духовной дуэли, проводимой на уровне, который никто за пределами их касты не может различить. Некоторые Эфирные существа носят свои Клинки Чести на поле битвы, не ожидая, что им придется их использовать, но, тем не менее, готовые дать последний отпор своим врагам.</OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.description>
                               <!-- handle -->
<OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.tools.0.label>handle</OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.tools.0.label>
                               <!-- head -->
<OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.tools.1.label>head</OGT_Melee_HonorBlade.tools.1.label>

</LanguageData>
