<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<!--/Defs/ThingDefs_Misc/Weapons/OG_AMA_Weapons_Chaos_Ranged_Bolt.xml-->
                     <!-- bolt pistol (C) -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltPistol.label>bolt pistol (C)</OGC_Gun_BoltPistol.label>
                           <!-- A Bolt Pistol is a smaller version of the Bolter in standard use by the Space Marines and other Imperial forces such as the Orders Militant of the Adepta Sororitas and certain members of the Astra Militarum and the Imperial Navy. Powerful and utilitarian side arms, Bolt Pistols have seen service within many of the Imperium's military forces since its inception in the 30th Millennium. The current standard pattern in use amongst the Space Marines is the Mark III. Bolt Pistols are also used by many other Imperial forces as well as the Chaos Space Marines. A Bolt Pistol is commonly used in conjunction with a close combat weapon by Space Marine officers, Veterans and Assault Squads to make them into melee combat specialists. -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltPistol.description>A Bolt Pistol is a smaller version of the Bolter in standard use by the Space Marines and other Imperial forces such as the Orders Militant of the Adepta Sororitas and certain members of the Astra Militarum and the Imperial Navy. Powerful and utilitarian side arms, Bolt Pistols have seen service within many of the Imperium's military forces since its inception in the 30th Millennium. The current standard pattern in use amongst the Space Marines is the Mark III. Bolt Pistols are also used by many other Imperial forces as well as the Chaos Space Marines. A Bolt Pistol is commonly used in conjunction with a close combat weapon by Space Marine officers, Veterans and Assault Squads to make them into melee combat specialists.</OGC_Gun_BoltPistol.description>
                             <!-- stock -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltPistol.tools.0.label>stock</OGC_Gun_BoltPistol.tools.0.label>
                  <!-- bolter (C) -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltGun.label>bolter (C)</OGC_Gun_BoltGun.label>
                        <!-- The Bolter, also called a Boltgun, and its variants are some of the most powerful hand-held ballistic anti-personnel weaponry in use by the military forces of the Imperium of Man. It is a powerful assault weapon that fires explosive kinetic rounds colloquially referred to as bolts. The Bolter is a weapon synonymous with the Adeptus Astartes, and rightly so. However, although the Space Marines are its primary users, the Bolter finds itself in use in military organisations throughout the Imperium. The weapon is fearsome, with explosive rounds capable of ripping through or blowing apart a foe. The Chaos Space Marines of the Traitor Legions were issued their Legions' Bolters before the Horus Heresy, and therefore use generally older variants than the patterns available to present-day Loyalist Space Marines. -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltGun.description>The Bolter, also called a Boltgun, and its variants are some of the most powerful hand-held ballistic anti-personnel weaponry in use by the military forces of the Imperium of Man. It is a powerful assault weapon that fires explosive kinetic rounds colloquially referred to as bolts. The Bolter is a weapon synonymous with the Adeptus Astartes, and rightly so. However, although the Space Marines are its primary users, the Bolter finds itself in use in military organisations throughout the Imperium. The weapon is fearsome, with explosive rounds capable of ripping through or blowing apart a foe. The Chaos Space Marines of the Traitor Legions were issued their Legions' Bolters before the Horus Heresy, and therefore use generally older variants than the patterns available to present-day Loyalist Space Marines.</OGC_Gun_BoltGun.description>
                          <!-- stock -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltGun.tools.0.label>stock</OGC_Gun_BoltGun.tools.0.label>
                          <!-- barrel -->
<OGC_Gun_BoltGun.tools.1.label>barrel</OGC_Gun_BoltGun.tools.1.label>
                      <!-- storm bolter (C) -->
<OGC_Gun_StormBolter.label>storm bolter (C)</OGC_Gun_StormBolter.label>
                            <!-- The Storm Bolter is a double-barrelled version of the standard .75 calibre Bolter. As it is heavier and causes more recoil than a normal Bolter, it is even more rarely used than the Bolter by the regiments of the Astra Militarum. Instead, Storm Bolters are the standard weapons employed by Space Marine Terminators or as a pintle-mounted weapon on an Imperial main battle tank. Storm Bolters are also used by the Astartes of the Grey Knights Chapter as a gauntlet-mounted weapon with its feed located on the rear of their armour. The Storm Bolter also sees limited use amongst the Orders Militant of the Adepta Sororitas, where it is considered a specialist weapon, and favoured by those squads of Dominions, the Sororitas' heavy-weapons troops, who prefer to engage in mid-range, anti-infantry combat. -->
<OGC_Gun_StormBolter.description>The Storm Bolter is a double-barrelled version of the standard .75 calibre Bolter. As it is heavier and causes more recoil than a normal Bolter, it is even more rarely used than the Bolter by the regiments of the Astra Militarum. Instead, Storm Bolters are the standard weapons employed by Space Marine Terminators or as a pintle-mounted weapon on an Imperial main battle tank. Storm Bolters are also used by the Astartes of the Grey Knights Chapter as a gauntlet-mounted weapon with its feed located on the rear of their armour. The Storm Bolter also sees limited use amongst the Orders Militant of the Adepta Sororitas, where it is considered a specialist weapon, and favoured by those squads of Dominions, the Sororitas' heavy-weapons troops, who prefer to engage in mid-range, anti-infantry combat.</OGC_Gun_StormBolter.description>
                              <!-- stock -->
<OGC_Gun_StormBolter.tools.0.label>stock</OGC_Gun_StormBolter.tools.0.label>
                              <!-- barrel -->
<OGC_Gun_StormBolter.tools.1.label>barrel</OGC_Gun_StormBolter.tools.1.label>
                      <!-- heavy bolter (C) -->
<OGC_Gun_HeavyBolter.label>heavy bolter (C)</OGC_Gun_HeavyBolter.label>
                            <!-- A Heavy Bolter is a powerful Bolt Weapon that is used for anti-infantry and fire support roles, and is also known as the "Backbreaker" or the "Bruiser" because of its great weight and the amount of damage it can deal. Unlike the Boltgun, it is relatively common in Imperial Guard armies and is also often used by the Space Marines. Heavy Bolters have a high rate of fire and are relatively cheap to field. A Heavy Bolter can also be mounted on the cupola pintle-mounts of a wide variety of Imperial armoured vehicles, as well as act as an anti-personnel weapon by Imperial fixed defences, including strongholds and other fortifications. -->
<OGC_Gun_HeavyBolter.description>A Heavy Bolter is a powerful Bolt Weapon that is used for anti-infantry and fire support roles, and is also known as the "Backbreaker" or the "Bruiser" because of its great weight and the amount of damage it can deal. Unlike the Boltgun, it is relatively common in Imperial Guard armies and is also often used by the Space Marines. Heavy Bolters have a high rate of fire and are relatively cheap to field. A Heavy Bolter can also be mounted on the cupola pintle-mounts of a wide variety of Imperial armoured vehicles, as well as act as an anti-personnel weapon by Imperial fixed defences, including strongholds and other fortifications.</OGC_Gun_HeavyBolter.description>
                              <!-- barrel -->
<OGC_Gun_HeavyBolter.tools.0.label>barrel</OGC_Gun_HeavyBolter.tools.0.label>

</LanguageData>
